<TxFileSystem.BaseDocs>
   <Extensions>
      <FileSystemProperties>
         <FileSystemProperty modifying="true">
           <remarks>
             <para>
               Depending on the method of this object's instance being invoked the journal is used or 
               not. Backup and restore takes place depending on the state of the journal.
             </para>
           </remarks>
           <value>
             <para>
               This object instance contains both methods that modify file system resources and methods 
               that don't modify any of them.
             </para>
           </value>
         </FileSystemProperty>
         <FileSystemProperty modifying="false">
            <remarks>
              <para>
                This object instance only contains methods that don't modify any file system resources.
                Regardless of which of this object's methods is being invoked journalizing and, backup 
                and restore, never take place.
              </para>
            </remarks>
         </FileSystemProperty>
      </FileSystemProperties>
      <Operations>      
         <Operation kind="FileOperation" type="modify">
            <remarks>
              <para>
                This is an operation that modifies one or more files, hence it is journalized. 
                Journalized file operations can either be rolled back or committed automatically, 
                restoring or removing the backup file(s), respectively. Whenever an <see 
                  cref="System.Exception"/> of any kind occurs, all journalized operations are 
                rolled back, resulting in the original state to be restored.
              </para>
              <para>
                If no <see cref="System.Exception"/> any kind occurs and the <see 
                cref="System.Transactions.TransactionScope" /> completes successfully, all journalized
                operations are committed. Any modifications made are then preserved and the backup file(s)
                are then removed.
              </para>
              <see href="https://txfilesystem.io/docs/FileOperation" />
            </remarks>
         </Operation>      
         <Operation kind="FileOperation" type="info">
            <remarks>
              <para>
                This is an operation that doesn't modify any files, hence it is not journalized. As there
                is no need to rollback any modifications whenever an <see cref="System.Exception"/> of any
                kind occurs inside a <see cref="System.Transactions.TransactionScope" />.
              </para>
              <see href="https://txfilesystem.io/docs/FileOperation" />
            </remarks>
         </Operation>
         <Operation kind="DirectoryOperation" type="create">
            <remarks>
              <para>
                This is an operation that creates a directory, hence it is journalized. Journalized file 
                operations can either be rolled back or committed automatically, removing or keeping the
                created directory, respectively. Whenever an <see cref="System.Exception"/> of any kind 
                occurs, all journalized operations are rolled back, resulting in the original state to 
                be restored.
              </para>
              <para>
                If no <see cref="System.Exception"/> any kind occurs and the <see 
                cref="System.Transactions.TransactionScope" /> completes successfully, all journalized
                operations are committed. Any modifications made are then preserved.
              </para>
              <see href="https://txfilesystem.io/docs/DirectoryOperation" />
            </remarks>
         </Operation>
         <Operation kind="DirectoryOperation" type="delete">
            <remarks>
              <para>
                This is an operation that deletes a directory, hence it is journalized. Journalized file 
                operations can either be rolled back or committed automatically, restoring or keeping the
                directory deleted, respectively. Whenever an <see cref="System.Exception"/> of any kind 
                occurs, all journalized operations are rolled back, resulting in the original state to 
                be restored.
              </para>
              <para>
                If no <see cref="System.Exception"/> any kind occurs and the <see 
                cref="System.Transactions.TransactionScope" /> completes successfully, all journalized
                operations are committed. Any modifications made are then preserved.
              </para>
              <see href="https://txfilesystem.io/docs/DirectoryOperation" />
            </remarks>
         </Operation>
         <Operation kind="DirectoryOperation" type="info">
            <remarks>
              <para>
                This is an operation that returns information about the directory or its contents, hence 
                it is not journalized. There is no need for the operation to be rolled back.
              </para>
              <see href="https://txfilesystem.io/docs/DirectoryOperation" />
            </remarks>
         </Operation>
         <Operation kind="DirectoryOperation" type="modify">
            <remarks>
              <para>
                This is an operation that modifies a directory and/or its contents, hence it is 
                journalized. Journalized file operations can either be rolled back or committed 
                automatically, restoring or removing the backup directory and its contents,
                respectively. Whenever an <see cref="System.Exception"/> of any kind occurs, all 
                journalized operations are rolled back, resulting in the original state to be 
                restored.
              </para>
              <para>
                If no <see cref="System.Exception"/> any kind occurs and the <see
                cref="System.Transactions.TransactionScope" /> completes successfully, all journalized
                operations are committed. Any modifications made are then preserved and the backup 
                directory and its contents is then removed.
              </para>
              <see href="https://txfilesystem.io/docs/DirectoryOperation" />
            </remarks>
         </Operation>
         <Operation kind="FileSystemOperation" type="info">
            <remarks>
              <para>
                This is an operation that returns information about the file system, hence it is not 
                journalized. There is no need for the operation to be rolled back.
              </para>
              <see href="https://txfilesystem.io/docs/DirectoryOperation" />
            </remarks>
         </Operation>
      </Operations>
   </Extensions>
</TxFileSystem.BaseDocs>